Flames everywhere! What is happening?!
I'm the one doing the murdering!
I'm the Land of Wano's supreme ruler!
Kill! Kill! kiiiill them!
To hell with you, Kaido!
to To hell with your third-rate "New Onigashima Project"!
Orochi!
So you are behind this!
Oh, what do we have here? The Kozuki's parade of ghouls!
Orochi-sama...
They are unaware that you have already died once.
Fukurokuju!
Please, escape. Allow me to handle them...
Stand down, fool!
Battered and bruised, are we... Well, you would be, wouldn't you?
You volunteered yourselves to die, after all!
Completely lost your sanity, every last one of you!
Listen here! I'm going to...
...absolutely, positively have all of your heads!
Come at me... We will do battle right here!
Do you know just who it is you face?!
Know your place, filth!
I am the Shogun of the Land of Wano!
What insolence is this?! I am not the villain here!
I merely gave the Kozuki clan what was coming to them!
I merely took back what was mine!
But you idiots fail to understand...
Peasants and samurai all bow before their Shogun, and obey his word!
I am a man of power!
Flower Shuriken!
The true villains are my oppressors — this nation!
Th-That look in your eyes!
Are you trying to tell me that I'm wrong?!
Don't look at me!
I cannot be wrong!
Stop looking at me like that!
Orochi-sama!
Hell shall be your judge! Let us be off!
Will you avenge your lord, then?
I raised my opinion of you, Fukurokuju!
A fool though he was, you remained loyal to him 'til the end..
I could say the same of all of you!
Even without seeking vengeance, you and I were destined to fight
You understand, do you not... Raizo!
Aye!
Reach your hands out,
cut through the wind,
and forge ahead, drawing your own map as you go!
We can't even tell left from right
in this tempest-tossed era
Even the values we've honed
seem ready to crumble
Is the compass leading us true,
or is it leading us astray?
Nobody knows for sure!
# Just breathe deep, close your eyes
and you'll find your soul guiding the way!
Reach your hands out,
cut through the wind,
and kick away the darkness!
* and you're doing this for yourself too, right?
Forge ahead, painting the world in your own colors!
#  Edited by fedew Subtitles by HatSubs
Dealing with both of them at the same time is such a pain in the ass.
Yeah... This ain't doin' any wonders for my health.
Whaddya say we stick it to 'em, Kaido?
Wonder which of those five'll live to tell the tale...
Trafalgar! Can't you move either of them down below with your ability?
If I could, I would've done it already.
Their Haki's too much for me... I can't move them!
Well, then... How's about we tear 'em apart?
Hey, here comes the big one!
0/00 0
Hope you've still got strong legs, hag!
Who do you think you're talking to, brat?!
Supremacy High Seas Supremacy!
Freakin' unreal!
Not happening! There's no dodging that!
Get outta here, guys!
300,08
Just staying there...
...is gonna get you dead!
Zoro!
They're nowhere to be seen, but I can still hear their voices...
They got away from it, huh.. Color me impressed.
Zoroer, you still breathing?
I think so...
Hell of a job holding that back, even for just a moment. Thanks.
Where's Straw Hat?
Kaido!
Gum-Gum...
..Red...
Made ya jump, Kaido!
Must be 'cause it hurts!
Stick it to 'em!
Damned jackasses!
Thanks!
Kaido!
Conqueror of Three Worlds:
Ragnaraku!
Luffy!
Let's take out the rest of the trash, too!
Done!
Okay!
Room:
H Chambres!
Where am I?! It's dark in here!
Zeus!
Can you do it, Roronoa?!
Ain't like I got a choice!
I'm not lettin' you put yourself back together!
Flame Rend: Crossing the Six Paths!
Stop! I'm just a sword!
Mama, save me!
My children!
Now's our chance!
Punk Pistols!
What's this, now?!
Did you really think you could beat me by cutting me off from them?!
Repel!
Takt!
Idiots! I won't be done in by having rocks thrown at me!
Oh, damn it!
Mama!
If he can't fly down to help her, then that takes care of one of them!
How d'ya like that?!
Save me, right now!
Zeuuuus!
Mama!
What's wrong, Mama?!
Go on, cry! Scream for me!
Say goodbye to the old bag!
The sea...
...will take care of the rest.
Buwhat are byou doinbu?!
Probmetheusbu!
Mama! I'm on my wa=
Mama! I'm com-
That moron...
High Seas Supremacy!
Freakin' unreal!
Not happening! There's no dodging that!
Get outta here, guys!
00,0,00
Zoro!
How did he not have every bone in his body shattered from taking that?!
Pathetic, Linlin!
Do I gotta do everything for you?
Hey, Pirate Hunter!
Let Prometheus go!
Chambres!
Injection Shot!
I'm really not liking that ability of yours...
...Trafalgar!
Curtain!
Mama!
Go away!
Maaamaaa!
Hey, Traf!
That fire thing's...
...on its way to save Big Mom!
Just let him go...
I'd rather the plan fail..
..than one of us die.
Mama!
What's going on, Mama?!
Our goal was to tear Big Mom and Kaido apart!
The rest of ya don't gotta put your lives on the line!
Leave Big Mom to me!
Mama!
My savior!
Thank goodness, Mama!
ew
You're so precious, yes you are,
Prometheus!
On the other hand...
What the hell is Zeus doing?!
He's useless to me!
l...
looo
...agree, Mama!
He's always so clumsy and slow.
He does not get to call himself our family anymore!
Hey, hey, I got something to ask you, Mama!
What's that?
The thing is... I want a girlfriend!
That's a good idea!
A new partner for Prometheus...
A new child to replace Zeus...
How will this child of mine turn out, I wonder?
It's... just like the last time!
11 111 111111
He's knocked out, but he's still...
...glaring at me!
Maybe I oughta...
...smash those eyes in first?
Or maybe...
...his brain?
Or his heart?
Traf.
I'm about to show this guy...
.exactly what I'm made of.
Zoroer!
Sloppy fighting...
...is only gonna wear us down.
If this don't work... It was just my time.
Then everything else..
...i's up to you!
Hey, Kaido!
That's our captain!
Why don'tcha give...
...bashin' my head in a try first?!
Demonic Aura...
Nine-Sword Style,
Ashura:
Blades Drawn!
Nine-Sword Style...
CIII
AS BL
Ashura: Blades Drawn
Dead Man's Game!
Damn!
This whelp...
You possess Conqueror's Haki too?!
What are you talking about?
You're making no sense!
I put everything I had into that one attack! 11
You could've at least fallen over... Would've liked that...
You did enough.
This scar's gonna be permanent.
LEATA
Pain-in-my-ass generation.
Hey! Zoroer, run!
You stay there... I'll come to you!
Thunder Bagua!
Shame...
Come with me, and we can rule the world...
With you?
Who'd wanna join your crew?
Ya jerk.
We...
...love the samurai.
I'm definitely gonna kick your ass...
You?
Kick my ass?
I'd love to see you try!
That is, if you even can...
...with fists that are all bark, no bite!
11 11
Don't strain yourself, now!
It's an immensely strong power, capable of defending you like invisible armor,
but it can also be altered / for use in offense.
However, if you take it one step further,
the Haki covering you strengthens even more,
entering the body of your foe and destroying it from the inside!
So don't strain yourself!
Flow the Haki from the parts of your body that don't need it into your fists.
Kong Gun!
Still not deep enough..
I figured somethin' out when you hit me with your spiked club.
You can "cover" things in Conqueror's Haki too, huh?
How's knowing that gonna help you?
You really think you can do that?
Only a handful...
...of the world's strongest can pull it off!
Not some dead man walking!
Don't strain yourself.
Flow the Haki from the parts of your body that don't need it into your fists.
Punk!
11 I put everything I had 111 into that one attack!
Pain-in-my-ass generation.
You're fighting a true monster!
But you definitely have it in you!
He's not even touching him..!
=1
Zoro...
Traf...
Thanks for keepin' me safe.
Get below, the both of ya!
Whatever happens to me... I'm going to beat him!
111 111
Tell everybody for me.. -
.. said that!
CONIINUED